(Sheldon:)- Hello.
- Hello.
(Blonde Girl:)I'm Alicia. I'm moving in upstairs.
(Leonard:)That is so great.
(Leonard:)Oh, I'm Leonard. I live downstairs.
(Leonard:)Upstairs from here, but under you.
(Leonard:)Not under you per se...
...but under your apartment. Heh-heh.
- That's nice.
- Yeah, it is.
Well, that concludes your faltering attempt
to mate.
(Sheldon:)- Hello.
- Hello.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)On a scale of one to ten, how light
of foot would you describe yourself...
(Sheldon:)...with one being not cat-like at all,
and ten being freakishly feline?
(Sheldon:)Freakishly feline?
(Sheldon:)Is that your answer
or do you not understand the question?
(Sheldon:)- We'll come back to that one.
- Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Hang on. Are you now or have you ever
been a salsa, Irish-folk or breakdancer?